boba_fett = [
    {
        "question": "1. Boba Fett debuted in the Star Wars Holiday Special as a ____ character.",
        "choices": ["k-drama", "cartoon", "anime", "alien"],
        "answer": "cartoon"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. Boba Fett is a ____",
        "choices": ["clone", "bounty hunter", "mandalorian", "all of these"],
        "answer": "all of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "3. Boba was revealed to be a clone created on the planet ____.",
        "choices": ["Colu", "Kamino", "Mars", "sub Neptune"],
        "answer": "Kamino"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. Boba was the only ____ clone.",
        "choices": ["unaltered", "sane", "humane", "funny"],
        "answer": "unaltered"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. Boba watched Jango get defeated by a Jedi in the Battle of ____.",
        "choices": ["Waterloo", "Panipat", "Geonosis", "Krypton"],
        "answer": "Geonosis"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. Boba almost dueled bounty hunter ____ in The Clone Wars.",
        "choices": ["Mad Kane", "Bad Bane", "Chad Kane", "Cad Bane"],
        "answer": "Cad Bane"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. Boba hunted ____ before The Empire Strikes Back.",
        "choices": ["Puke", "Ryuk", "Luke", "Zeuk"],
        "answer": "Luke"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. In Legends canon, he eventually escaped the sarlacc pit.",
        "choices": ["Don't know", "True", "False", "None of these"],
        "answer": "True"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Mark Hamill wanted Boba to be revealed as Luke's ____.",
        "choices": ["father", "brother", "apprentice", "mother"],
        "answer": "mother"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. Lucas almost made Boba Fett Anakin's ____.",
        "choices": ["uncle", "sister", "brother", "master"],
        "answer": "brother"
    },
]